是的  福瑞克女士没有尽到
Yes, Mrs. Florrick did not demonstrate
我所期望的义务
the duty of care I would expect.
如果她尽到了呢
And if she had?
如果她快速有效地向我传达了信息
If she had informed me promptly and efficiently,
有可能会对瑞格先生的保释案有更好的了解
I might've had a better context to set Mr. Riggs' bail.
那你需要再尽力
Should you have done more to try to pull
向她索取信息吗
that information out of her?
我的职责是裁决
My role is to adjudicate.
不是辩护
Not advocate.
是这样  我把沙考斯基法庭的
All right, well, I went through the transcripts
法庭记录  想找一下不当行为
from Schakowsky's courtroom, looking for abuses,
找找有没有罚律师提高保释金
looking for any mention of taxing lawyers.
然后呢
And?
什么也没找到
Nothing.
没有任何关于加罚金的记录
Not a single mention of taxing.
他每次说的时候都会盖住麦克风
He always covers the microphone when he says it.